Mizuki Yamashita's last campaign
In prayer for the success of our 35th single
I was challenged to do the trapeze by Kinoshita Grand Circus.
but the result was not so funny.
It's the last time I'm going to pray for a hit.
I thought I couldn't end it like this.
I wanted to do something else for Nogizaka.
I thought I could do something for everyone that would benefit Nogizaka in some other way.
I also thought about it and decided to do what Nogizaka's hit prayer originated from
I'd like to start handing out tissues now.
Yamashita chose a campaign to distribute 460 tissues in one day
Yamashita chose a campaign to distribute 460 tissues in one day by just one person
at various locations in Tokyo.
Yamashita disguised himself and handed out the tissues
to promote Nogizaka's new song to people who don't know Nogizaka yet.
Aiming to attract new fans for the future of the group
The first place I went to was Tokyo Tower.
I wonder... I just glanced at it...
I saw a lot of kindergarteners walking around.
Also, there are a lot of people from overseas.
I'm sure we'll be able to distribute it to a wide range of people.
I'm scared.
What if someone throws them away?
I remember the video of my seniors handing out tissues.
I remember it so vividly.
I think I was still in the first year of junior high school.
I think I was 13 years old.
I used to see people handing out tissues on the street
I used to see them on the street.
But how hard could it be? Like, are you crying? Crying?
I had a strong impression of tears.
I'm a little nervous about being alone this time.
But I'm sure I'll get rejected.
I don't want to lose heart. We have until the end of the night.
I'll be here until the end of the night, so I'll speak out and do my best.
Mizuki Yamashita's last campaign will start near the entrance to Tokyo Tower.
We'll start near the entrance of Tokyo Tower.
I'm so nervous!
I'll ask for your help.
Oh, no!
It's so hard!
It's so hard to get through...
It's full of people from overseas!
Excuse me, please.
Thank you very much.
Here you go.
I'm so glad I got the first one!
I finally succeeded in getting my first tissue!
And Yamashita...
Please.
Oh, no.
Thank you.
It didn't work.
Please
Thank you
Successful first inbound tish!
Steady start in appealing to foreigners...
9:00 a.m.
Tokyo Tower was under a light drizzle and the number of people was very sparse.
We couldn't get as many people as we wanted.
Still, we continued to call out to everyone who passed by.
Thank you very much.
Please do
Thank you
Cute.
Please.
Thank you.
Thank you
Thank you very much.
Hi, I'm Nogizaka.
Nogizaka?
That's great.
That's great. I'm so happy.
I'm a Nogizaka, too.
Really?
Yes. Are you a Nogizaka too?
Yes, I am.
What do you do?
I'm Mizuki Yamashita.
Do you know him?
Yes, I do.
Wow.
The first foreigner to be exposed this time.
I've been exposed!
After that, Yamashita continued to aggressively attack tourists from overseas.
And then...
Yamashita aggressively attacking foreign tourists
Information
OK, thank you!
Yamashita, now a resident of Tokyo Tower
After this, he picked up the pace even more.
and the number of tissues he handed out reached 50!
Surprisingly good!
I really feel like I'm doing a good job.
that we are spreading the word properly.
I'm so grateful!
Surprisingly, people overseas are more willing to give them to us
I'm glad.
I'm going to keep on doing well at Tokyo Tower.
Yamashita is going to continue to make more and more items.
Thank you very much!
Then you get used to the simple work
I guess my mind has become more relaxed.
Good night.
After that, it's time for the flow of people at Tokyo Tower.
Yamashita handed out tissues for about an hour without taking a break.
After handing out 124 tissues, far more than he had expected
at the scheduled time.
At the end of the day, he thanked
and also to the information lady.
to the next spot!
Handing out tissues is really hard work, isn't it?
I think it's really hard work!
I didn't know it was this hard.
But I feel like I'm spreading the word with my own hands.
It's nice to do something like this, it brings me back to my roots.
I'm going to Hanayashiki in Asakusa.
I'm going to Hanayashiki in Asakusa, but I'm not sure if there will be a lot of customers yet.
I'm going to Asakusa Hanayashiki, but I think the clientele is still a little different.
I'm going to the Hanayashiki.
I'm going to Hanayashiki in Asakusa.
I would like to distribute it to a wide range of people.
And so, next...
weekday morning at Asakusa Hanayashiki.
Since the purpose of this event is an amusement park, it was difficult to get people interested in the Yamashita tissues.
We had a hard time at first!
So cute!
Good night.
Thank you very much.
So cute!
He's here.
I dropped it.
Brothers.
And there they are... the lucky brothers.
To all the families, Yamashita Tissue was a big hit right away.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much
Please, thank you, thank you, thank you
Please, please, thank you, thank you
They all got it.
All the way, all the way, all the way.
Oh, they're calling it the Panther Disease Cell.
I'm so glad.
They're really paying attention.
I wish you'd listen to me.
Please do.
Thank you very much.
Thank you if you don't mind.
Wancer, please.
I'm glad you enjoy it
Thank you very much
bye bye
I'm glad you like it.
Surprisingly undetectable
Handing out tissues in this style.
It's not bad, right?
Yes, sir.
I don't know.
The flow of people stopped here and the pace slowed down.
Yamashita realized that there was a limit to what he could do just by waiting
Yamashita realized that there was no longer a limit to just waiting, so he changed his strategy to moving around and handing them to people as they passed by.
What's more
Yamashita has established a 100% successful pattern
established a 100% successful pattern.
After that, he continued to parade around the park
Yamashita continued to hand out tissues without a break, and once again achieved 100 tissues!
Surprisingly, no one saw him because everyone was absorbed in the rides.
But then he let his guard down and just handed out tissues.
Occupational hazard... waving hands.
I said, "Thank you very much.
I'm pretty sure the lady handing out the tissues didn't even do that.
But I'm getting used to it, and it's really nice.
Then I thanked her again for her cooperation.
We finished with no valuables for the first time in Hanayashiki!
Next, we moved to a shopping district in Tokyo and resumed handing out tissues.
It's hard to sell fish!
Struggling with the calm street and clientele
Then, Mr. Yamashita decided to make a bold move.
Since he didn't seem to have to worry about being noticed
I'd like to take off my glasses.
I'd like to look you in the eye and say hello a lot.
Please do. Thank you.
The rate of reception is higher with this nebula removed
Yamashita, who is gaining momentum with the lagaon release, will be even more
Thank you very much.
I don't think you guys here will recognize me.
I'd like to try the full Yamashita Challenge without the mask.
I can do it today. I don't think they'll notice.
Here's Yamashita at last, handing out tissues at 100%!
I'm happy because I can do it with a smile on my face.
Please. Thank you. Thank you.
They know.
I wonder if they know me.
The two guys who probably know Yamashita...
They didn't think it was real and didn't accept the tissue.
After that, they continued with the Yamashita challenge, but...
But the number of pedestrians was decreasing.
Finally, we went around to the stores in the shopping arcade and handed out the tissues.
At the Fukagawa Fudosan Shotenkai, we got 77 tissues!
Thank you very much.
The next place we handed out tissues was
Tower Records Shibuya Store!
Oh my God, here they come!
I think this is the most difficult place I've been to today!
The demographics of the people walking around are totally different.
But I don't know... so far they've been handing out a lot of these.
I'm getting used to it, aren't I?
I'm used to Tokyo as the girl handing out Kleenex.
It's surprisingly easy to be recognized.
I come here a lot in my private life.
I've never been spotted at the Tower Records Shibuya store.
But I've never been exposed in private.
I've never been exposed in private.
Maybe they buy Nogizaka's CDs or DVDs and come here to buy them.
There might be people there today.
And that's exactly why I'm here.
I'm here at the panel shop and I've even appeared on stage.
I'm sure there are many people who know Nogizaka.
I'm going to target that demographic.
Yamashita finally arrived in the big city of Shibuya
Will he be able to hand out the tissues?
Thank you very much.
They're here.
I'm so nervous, it's so different from before
Thank you very much.
It's so different... it's a big city...
Yamashita was flustered by the difference in the number of people, but surprisingly, he was able to hand out the tissues without being noticed.
I'm going to upload Yamashita's door here too, and try to get him to fold up the tissues.
Thank you very much.
I didn't expect to be seen from so far away.
Please. Thank you. Thank you.
Please. Thank you.
Come in. Thank you.
Wow. They thought I was a waitress, so I was attracted to you.
Thank you.
Yamashita thought he could go further.
And more...
Good.
But I can go further.
You all think of me as a sales clerk.
I'll do my best with the feeling of a shopkeeper too
With 80% Yamashita in store clerk mode.
I'm going to take on the streets of Shibuya at once
I win alone!
Thank you very much.
What?
What! Really?
That's great!
Thank you so much.
It's so obvious.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, you noticed?
Thank you very much.
That's so nice. Of course. Thank you so much.
Oh, my God, I'm going to crack.
Yamashita didn't even notice after that.
As expected, it was about to cause trouble for the store.
I had to leave much earlier than planned!
I'm really happy
I'm so happy, thank you so much!
Tower Records Shibuya for their cooperation
We finished with autographs and tissues.
Thank you so much!
Wow, they really know us!
Shibuya Tower Records is so obvious!
How many are you working on now?
The last one got caught.
If we can't do it here, 24...
What? Oh, no, we're not here.
24, how many more 110, 460?
Can you do it?
Yes, sir.
Next, we're in front of Alta in Shinjuku.
Shibuya was too crowded, so it was pretty obvious right away.
It's great. It was like a second.
Are you watching the drama? It was like...
Nogizaka, right? something like that...
It's the month of March, right? Like that.
I was so happy to hear that.
I think there are a lot of people in Shinjuku who like Nogizaka.
I'm trying my best not to be recognized.
Yamashita is worried that he won't be able to do the big city challenge for a long time, so he has come up with a secret plan.
Yamashita had a secret plan!
by wearing sunglasses at Shinjuku Alta.
Yamashita hoping for a "Tamorisun Boost" and a "Tamoribosu"!
Start handing out tissues!
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much
I'm nervous. Now that they think I'm cheap.
Please. Thank you very much.
Are you a member of Nogizaka? Yes, I am. Thank you very much.
I'm sorry, if you like my new song. Please listen to it.
Mika Yamashita? Yes, thank you.
Do you understand? Yes, I understand.
I've been exposed.
Power up, Tamori-san.
Please. Thank you.
Five in a row.
Thank you.
Surprisingly, they didn't notice.
Thrilling.
It's fun.
I'm doing so well.
I'm going to take my sunglasses off now for an extra boost.
What do you think? I don't think they're gonna notice.
Please, please, please, please.
Thank you for your hard work.
Yamashita lost Tamori-san's labor power
Unexpectedly, he was in a very bad condition
The number of people coming in and out of the booth was getting fewer and fewer
The number of visitors decreased, and the number of booths in front of Alta stopped at 47.
I was surprised to see a big brake at Shibuya and Shinjuku.
Will he be able to reach 460 at the remaining two locations?
Next, we went to the Sunshine Aquarium in Ikebukuro.
Sunshine Aquarium
I used to visit this aquarium with my family when I was a child.
I never thought that at the age of 24
I never thought that I would be handing out my single release
I never thought that the day would come when I would be handing out tissues for my single release
I've never thought that I'd be handing out my own singles here at the age of 24.
I was wearing sunglasses in Shinjuku a while ago.
I was wearing sunglasses in Shinjuku earlier and some fans noticed me.
I guess it doesn't matter if I'm wearing a disguise or not after all.
People who notice me notice me.
and those who don't notice don't notice.
So we have prepared a secret plan for this event.
So this time, we have a little more secret plan.
So we went undercover at the Sunshine Aquarium.
What is the second secret that Yamashita has prepared?
It's a lot of fun!
We can see penguins and flamingos at the same time!
That's nice and equal!
Turning into a flamingo at the Yamashita Aquarium!
A bold plan to attract attention with a very flashy pink color!
But...
I chose pink flamingos!
The timing of my visit was bad, and few visitors passed by.
And because of the conspicuousness of the bright pink
It made us look more suspicious than a normal quiche vendor, which drove away customers even more.
And because of the cold weather, the thinly clad pinks reached the limit of their activity.
After that, we tried our best without a break, but we couldn't distribute as much as we wanted to.
The time was up without seeing them!
Finally, we handed the tissues to the PR person who had been so kind to us...
Please listen to our new song if you like.
Thank you very much!
I like Mizuki Umeshita this year.
What?
I've fallen in love with Umesaka.
Really? Really?
I'm very happy to hear that.
What?
I've been looking at it with a peaceful heart.
I'm so glad.
Thank you. - No, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
We've just received the biggest reaction from the public relations department at the aquarium.
We've handed out a total of 423 tissues in the past 10 hours.
There is only one place left.
Will we get them all by the end of the day?
Here we are at the last location!
Here we are at our last location!
Raraport Toyosu!
Thank you very much.
It's already pitch black outside.
It's unbelievable.
We started at 9:00.
It's getting late.
I can already see it.
When we're done distributing, we'll get to the finish line.
That's good, isn't it?
But I don't know... it's getting late.
I hope there won't be too many people.
I'm hoping there won't be too many people.
I'm a little anxious.
And I'm a bit nervous about standing alone next to the penguins dressed as a flamingo
standing alone next to the penguins dressed as a flamingo
I hope I can finish with a smile on my face.
I'll do my best.
There are only 37 tissues left!
We have about 45 minutes left on location before the last tissue!
We have 37 tissues left, and we'll be handing out our last tissues in about 45 minutes.
The last tissue distribution is about to begin.
The last tissue distribution has started!
Last spurt! Go for it!
Thank you very much.
Please. Thank you. Thank you.
They call me Nogizaka.
Please, please, please, thank you
We've been on our feet for more than 10 hours now, and the cold has taken our strength to the limit.
I'm going to do this location with a smile on my face.
Please, please, thank you
Determined to do so, E Masuda does his best to face the remaining tissues...
Please, please, please
If they don't pick them up when they get here, it'll be a mental blow...
Please, thank you
Oh, that's right
Thank you very much.
Here, look at these tissues.
I'm so glad.
Thank you.
I thought for a moment that I'd go up here and wait for you.
Thank you very much.
Please come and visit us again.
Thank you
Thank you very much.
I'm so happy!
Yamashita was cheered up by the smiles of his fans.
Finally, we moved to the LaLaPort.
Finally, the tissue distribution reached its climax.
There were only a few tissues left.
But the number of customers going home was increasing, and we could not get as many as we had hoped.
The last sudden brake
I can't even put my foot down!
Yamashita is getting impatient as the end time is approaching.
Still, he keeps trying with a determined smile on his face.
After the failure of the trapeze
The revenge project that he himself was also involved in
In order not to let the project end in failure
For the future of Nogizaka
Yamashita chose the starting point of praying for a hit
Handing out tissues
This time, he would finish the race alone
Sow the seeds of 460 new fans with a smile on my face
Keep moving forward without stopping
Wow, only 3 more to go!
Nogizaka46, thank you very much!
Thank you very much.
I see them.
I want people who don't know the group to know the name.
With this in mind, the words they distribute are filled with power.
Mizuki Yamashita
The last challenge as Nogizaka46
How will it end?
Nogizaka46, please!
Oh no, they won't take it!
What should I do?
I'm sorry, it's Nogizaka46, please!
What should I do with the last one?
Who should I drop it off to?
Excuse me, it's Nogizaka46, please!
And finally...
Excuse me, this is Nogizaka46, please.
Thank you very much.
Oh, he let go!
We've now handed out 460 tissues in the 11 hours since we started filming.
I'm so glad. Thank you very much. We're done.
What?
I don't know. It was crazy.
I was so anxious.
I didn't mean to cry.
I'm glad you had a smile on your face by the end.
I'm glad. I cried because I was so relieved.
I'm glad.
The first time I prayed for a hit, it was a complete disaster.
I was so scared until today.
I was afraid that if I failed, I wouldn't be able to get it back.
I couldn't imagine that, and that's why I was so scared.
I'm really relieved.
I felt like now I can graduate without opening my heart.
I'm crying tears of joy.
I'm so happy.
I joined Mugisaka.
I don't know... tears of relief...
I've never cried tears of joy before.
I've never done that before.
I'm glad.
I've been crying a lot lately.
Two weeks.
Like, three weeks ago.
I was crying because I couldn't fly.
I didn't think I'd cry
I didn't think I'd be crying because I made it through.
I'm glad. Thank you very much.
Yes, it's all over now.
Thank you all so much for listening to my selfishness.
Thank you so much!
So, the 35th single
The campaign was a great success!
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
Thank you for watching!